SHELDON: The entrance to the dungeon is a moss-covered door.
L'entrée du donjon est une porte pleine de mousse.
You manage to open it only to find yourself face-to-face...
Tu parviens à l'ouvrir et tombes face
...with a hideous, foul-smelling, moss-covered ogre.
à un ogre immonde, couvert de mousse.
What do you do?
Que fais—tu ?
I say, "Hey, Ma, what's for dinner?"
Je dis : "maman, on mange quoi ?"
Seventeen.
Dix-sept.
The ogre is amused by yourjoke and allows you to pass.
L‘ogre rit de votre blague et vous laisse passer.
By the by, I liked it too.
Moi aussi,j'ai bien aimé.
How go the wedding plans, Howard?
Ça avance, ce mariage ?
Great. Spent five hours last night at Macy's registering for gifts.
J'ai passé 5 heures chez Macy's hier, pour déposer une liste.
I'm finally gonna have that earthenware asparagus dish I've always wanted, heh.
Enfin, j‘aurai ce plat a asperges en grès dontje rêve.
See, this is the good thing about having a girlfriend 9000 miles away.
C‘est l‘avantage, quand ta copine est a 15 000 Km.
I can spend my nights doing whatever I want.
J'occupe mes soirées comme je veux.
Like playing nerd games with us...
En jouant avec nous
...and then taking a suspiciously long shower?
avant de prendre une douche très longue ?
Maybe.
Peut—ètre.
We enter the dungeon.
Nous entrons dans le donjon.
You see a dragon.
Tu vois un dragon.
Really? So we're playing Dungeons and Dragons.
Ah bon ? On joue a Donjons & Dragons,
And we walk into a dungeon and see a dragon?
et il y a un dragon dans un donjon ?
-lsn't that a little on the nose? -When you play Chutes and Ladders...
- Prévisible, non ? - Quand tu joues aux petits chevaux,
...do you complain about all the chutes and the ladders?
tu te plains de Ia sur-représentation équine ?
Are you gonna eat that whole pie?
Tu vas tout manger ?
Maybe. Why not?
Peut—ètre. Pourquoi pas ?
Who do I have in my life to watch my figure for?
Pour qui je ferais gaffe a ma ligne ?
Oh, God, did you watch Bridget Jones again?
Tu as encore regardé Bridget Jones ?
No, it's just that everybody's got someone.
Non. Mais tout le monde a quelqu‘un.
Sheldon's with Amy, Howard's getting married...
Sheldon a Amy, Howard se marrie,
-...you're dating my sister. -Now that Howard's getting married...
- tu sors avec ma sœur. - Peut—étre qu'Howard
...maybe he'll inflate one of his old girlfriends for you, heh.
te lègueras une de ses ex gonflables.
You know who I blame for my loneliness?
Et le responsable de ma solitude ?
The United States of America.
Les États—Unis.
Your movies and your TV shows...
Vos films, vos séries,
...promised streets paved with beautiful blonde women with big bazongas.
promettent des averses de blondes aux gros seins.
Eat another pie, you'll have your own bazongas.
Une tarte de plus et tu feras toi—mème du 90.
That's cruel. You know it goes straight to my hips.
Tu sais que je prends tout dans les hanches.
Gentlemen, please focus.
Messieurs, on se concentre.
-You're facing a fire-breathing dragon. -Unh, I don't know if I wanna play anymore.
- Vous affronte: un dragon. - Je ne veux plus jouer.
Because you don't have a girlfriend? If that becomes a reason...
Si ne pas avoir de copine empêche de jouer
...not to play Dungeons and Dragons, this game's in serious trouble.
a D&D, ce jeu va vite disparaître.
Now, I assume we use this same wax later on...
J‘imagine qu'on va utiliser cette cire
...to neaten up each other's bikini regions.
pour dégager nos maillots respectifs.
Yeah, my bikini region is fine.
Mon maillot va bien.
Who's shocked? I'm not.
Qui est choqué ? Pas moi.
So, Bernadette, how's the wedding planning going?
Alors, Bernadette, ça avance, le mariage ?
And I'm not asking as a prospective bridesmaid.
Non que je veuille être demoiselle d'honneur.
[IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE] Pick me. Pick me.
Choisis-moi. Choisis-moi.
We went cake tasting yesterday.
Hier, on a goûté des gâteaux.
Raj came along.
Avec Raj.
He cried and ate half the samples.
Il s‘est goinfré en pleurant.
Oh, poor guy. He's so lonely. We should set him up with someone.
Le pauvre, il est si seul. On devrait le caser.
You know, I met a really cute girl at work.
J'ai rencontré une fille mignonne, au boulot.
She's married to a guy in one of our drug trials.
L‘épouse d'un type, poursuivi pour trafic de drogue.
Well, hello? She's married, heh.
Réfléchis, elle est mariée.
Yeah, but her husband is in serious congestive heart failure...
Oui, mais son mari a de gros soucis cardiaques,
...and a little birdie told me he's in the placebo group.
et mon petit doigt me dit qu'il est dans le groupe placébo.
Okay, so future grief-stricken widow is the one to beat.
Ok, alors à l‘attaque sur la future veuve éplorée.
-You ready to order? -One moment.
- On commande ? - Attends.
I'm conducting an experiment.
Je mène une expérience.
With Dungeons and Dragons dice?
Avec des dés de Donjons & Dragons ?
Yes. From here on in...
Oui. A partir de maintenant,
...l've decided to make all trivial decisions with a throw of the dice.
toutes mes décisions anodines serontjouées aux dés.
Thus freeing up my mind to do what it does best...
Ce qui libère mon cerveau pour lui permettre
...enlighten and amaze.
de sidérer le monde entier.
Page 14, item seven.
Page 14, 7ème ligne.
So, what's for dinner?
Alors, quel est le menu ?
A side of corn succotash.
Une assiette de mais et de haricots bouillis.
Hmm, interesting.
Intéressant.
Um, Howard, can I see you for a minute, please?
Howard, tu as une minute ?
Ugh, I don't wanna show any more of your friends how I can fit in the booster seats.
Je ne veux plus prouver que je rentre dans un rehausseur.
Uh, no, that's not it. Just come with me, please?
C‘est pas ça. Tu peux venir ?
Let's see what I'll be washing that succotash down with.
Que vais-je boire avec mes haricots ?
A pitcher of margaritas.
Un pichet de margarita.
Do you really want that?
C‘est ce que tu veux ?
That's the great thing. It doesn't matter.
Tout est la : peu importe.
My mind is freed up to think about more important things.
Mon cerveau est libre de penser a des choses importantes.
What's it thinking about now?
Par exemple ?
Hamburgers and lemonade.
A des hamburgers et de Ia limonade.
Um, Raj, there's someone I want you to meet.
Raj, j'ai quelqu'un ate présenter.
This is my friend, Emily. I know her from spin class.
Voici mon amie, Emily. On fait de la gym ensemble.
No. Raj, relax. She can't hear you. She's deaf.
Du calme, Raj. Elle ne t'entend pas, elle est sourde.
Emily, this is our friend Raj.
Emily, voici notre ami Raj.
Look at you guys, just hitting it off. I am so good.
Ils s‘entendent déjà comme larrons en foire. J‘assure.
Hi.
Salut.
She says, "It's nice to meet you."
Elle dit : "enchantée".
Did she really mean that or was she signing it sarcastically?
Sincérement ? Ses signes ne sont pas sarcastiques ?
Raj says, "It's nice to meet you too." Heh.
Raj dit : "c‘est réciproque".
Uh, she says she has to go back to her family.
Elle doit aller retrouver sa famille.
But Penny has her number if you wanna text her and get together.
Mais Penny a son numéro, envoie—lui un sms pour la voir.
Okay, I'm gonna play it cool.
Ok, je vais lajouer cool.
Tell her, "Maybe. Whatever, babe."
Dis—lui : ”peut—être. On verra, ma poule."
He'll text you, heh.
Il t‘enverra un message.
I love America again.
J'aime l‘Amérique.
And now for dessert.
Maintenant, le dessert.
Come on, hot fudge sundae.
Allez, glace avec coulis de chocolat.
Bam! That's what I'm talking about.
Là, ça me plait.
Okay. As soon as she gets here, so she knows I'm cool with it...
Dès qu'elle arrivera, pour lui montrer que je suis cool,
...l'm going to make ajoke about her being deaf.
je vais faire une blague sur la surdité.
l was thinking, "Hey, did you hear the one about--?
Par exemple : "Tu as entendu parler de...
Oh, no, I bet you didn't."
Ah non, forcément."
Maybe we should revisit your lonely, fat guy plan, heh.
Finalement, seul et gros, c‘est peut-être ton avenir.
Oh, she's here.
Elle est la.
No joke.
Pas de blague.
-She's sorry she's late. -Oh, tell her it doesn't matter.
- Elie s'excuse de son retard. - Peu importe.
Tell her her eyes shimmer like opalescent lilies...
Ses yeux brillent tels les lys opalescents
...in the lake of the palace of the celestial maidens.
ornant le lac du palais des Vierges du paradis.
Really? That's the first thing you wanna say?
Vraiment ? Tu commences comme ça ?
-I worked on it all night. Use it. -I don't know the sign for "opalescent."
- J'ai bossé dessus. Dis—le. - “Opalescent", je sais pas faire.
-Then spell it. -I don't know how to spell it.
- Épelle. - Je sais pas l‘épeler.
You're blowing this for me.
Tu fous tout en l'air.
He likes your eyes, heh.
Il aime tes yeux.
You're making me sound like a caveman.
Tu me fais passer pour un rustre.
"Thank you, you have nice eyes too."
”Merci, tu as aussi de jolis yeux."
Really? Ask her how many children she wants...
Vraiment ? Combien d‘enfants veut-elie ?
...and whatever number she says, say, "Me too."
Quoi qu'elle réponde, dis : "moi aussi".
Fine. Tell her I have a deep, sexy voice like James Earl Jones.
D‘accord.
She doesn't know what James Earl Jones sounds like.
Elle ne connait pas la voix de James Earl Jones.
Great. Then she won't know I'm lying.
Parfait, elle ne saura pas que je mens.
Let's see, what else can I tell you about me that would make you like me?
Que puis-je dire qui te poussera a m‘apprécier ?
Oh, I love music.
J‘adore la musique.
Do you love music?
Et toi ?
You really wanna ask her that?
Tu veux vraiment demander ça ?
Oh. You're right. Heh, everyone loves music.
Tu as raison. Qui n'aime pas la musique ?
She says, "Do you play an instrument?"
Elle demande si tu joues d'un instrument.
No, but when l was 6 years old...
Non, mais quand j‘avais 6 ans,
...I tried to start a boy band called Frankie Goes to Bollywood.
j'ai voulu fonder un groupe: Frankie Goes to Bollywood.
But I couldn't get any other boys to join...
Mais aucun garçon ne voulait en être,
...so my parents asked the servants to be my backup dancers.
mes parents ont fait danser nos gens derrière moi.
Wait, when you sign servants, don't sign it like I'm bragging.
Surtout, ne signe pas "gens" comme si je me vantais.
Sign it in away that I sound humble, with just a hint of:
Fais-Ie de manière humble, avec un soupçon de :
"That's right, I had servants."
“eh oui, j‘avais des domestiques."
-Do you hear yourself? -Yes, but she doesn't.
- Tu t‘entends ? - Oui, mais pas elle.
So get signing, hand-monkey.
Alors au boulot, singe signant.
I think I wrote a letter to Santa Claus every day.
J'écrivais au Père Noël chaque jour.
And then on Christmas morning...
Et un Noël,
...under the tree is a little puppy with a red ribbon.
j'ai trouvé un chiot au pied du sapin.
-What are you doing? -Texting Bernadette I'm gonna be late.
Tu fais quoi ?
-Dude, what is she saying? -lt's a funny story about a puppy.
- Elle dit quoi ? - Un truc drôle, avec un chiot.
Just smile and laugh.
Souris, et rigole.
-Quick, stop smiling. -What? Why?
- Arrête, Vite. - Pourquoi ?
The puppy died. It choked on a doll head. Sad face, sad face.
Le chiot est mort étouffé en rongeant une poupée. Air triste.
It's a little hard to see with the city lights...
On la voit mal a cause des lumières,
...but that W-shaped constellation is Cassiopeia.
mais cette constellation en W, c‘est Cassiopée.
And she was the mother of Andromeda, who's over there.
La mère d'Androméde, qui est la.
Look, pretty stars.
Regarde, les jolies étoiles.
This is her car, heh.
C‘est sa voiture.
She hopes she can see you again sometime.
Elie espère te revoir.
Good, good. Uh....
Bien, bien.
Oh, boy, uh, help me out here. Does she want me to kiss her or not?
Aide-moi. Elle veut que je l'embrasse ou pas ?
I speak sign language, I don't read minds.
Je sais signer, pas lire dans les pensées.
-If you were me, would you kiss her? -Yeah, but I'm the make-out king.
Tu l'embrasserais ?
l was so smooth on that date.
J'ai assuré.
You? I made you smooth. You were an idiot.
C‘est grâce a moi, tu as été débile.
Whatever, dude. She kissed me.
Elle m‘a embrassé.
Yeah, well, it might have been on your lips, but it was my kiss.
Tes lèvres peut—être, mais c‘était mon baiser.
Fine. Let's agree she kissed both of us.
Ok, disons qu'elle nous a embrassés.
Okay.
Ok.
Mustache is looking good there, Sheldon.
Jolie moustache, Sheldon.
Don't thank me. Thank the dice.
C‘est grâce aux dés.
They told me what percentage of my face to shave.
Ils m‘ont indiqué quel pourcentage raser.
Why are you still doing this?
Pourquoi tu continues ?
Because it's working.
Parce que ça marche.
In the past few weeks, unburdened by trivial decisions...
Depuis quelques semaines, libéré de ces trivialités,
...l've co-authored two papers in notable peer-reviewed journals...
j'ai co-écrit deux papiers pour des journaux reconnus
...and I'm close to figuring out why the Large Hadron Collider...
etje devine pourquoi le grand collisionneur de Hadron
...has yet to isolate the Higgs boson particle.
n‘a pas encore trouvé le boson de Higgs.
You left out, got chafed testicles because you no longer wear underpants.
Et tu as les testicules brûlés car tu ne portes plus de slip.
The dice giveth and the dice taketh away.
Les voies des dés sont impénétrables.
-ls Raj out with Emily again? -Yeah. Every night for the last month.
- Raj est avec Emily ? - Comme chaque soir depuis un mois.
Wow. I can't believe he has a girlfriend.
C‘est dingue qu'il ait une copine.
Me neither.
Oui.
Here's some other fun news on the Raj-Emily front.
Quelques infos croustillantes a ce sujet.
He gave her a pair of diamond earrings and leased her a car.
Il lui a offert des boucles en diamant et loué une voiture.
You're kidding.
Tu plaisantes.
-Think she's taking advantage of him? -Oh, of course not.
- Elie profite de lui ? - Bien sûr que non.
She wouldn't do something like that. She's deaf.
Elle ne ferait pas un truc pareil. Elle est sourde.
Deaf women can't be gold diggers?
Une sourde ne peut pas être vénale ?
Handicapped people are nice, Leonard. Everyone knows that.
Les handicapés sont gentils. C‘est bien connu.
I actually have information about Raj that would be helpful with this discussion.
J'ai des informations qui pourraient éclairer vos propos.
Could you tell us?
Lesquelles ?
Let's see.
Voyons.
Snake eyes. Sorry, bud.
Double un. Désolé, mon pote.
Wait. Hang on. Doubles. Roll again.
Attends, un double, il faut relancer.
Okay, get this.
Ok, écoutez.
It doesn't matter if he's showering her with gifts...
Peu importe qu'il l'inonde de cadeaux,
...because the Koothrappalis are vastly wealthy.
car les Koothrappalis sont trés aisés.
-What do you mean "vastly wealthy"? -Well, "wealthy" means a lot of money.
- Comment ça ? - "Aisés", ça veut dire riche.
"Vastly" means even more. I'm not sure what's tripping you up.
"Trés", ça veut dire encore plus riche. Facile.
I know they have money. I don't think it's that much.
Ils ont de l‘argent, mais pas a ce point.
No, you're wrong. As you know, a few years ago...
Erreur. Il y a quelques années,
...I achieved one of my lesser dreams and became a notary public.
j'ai réalisé un rêve et suis devenu écrivain public.
Well, from time to time, I notarize banking documents for Raj.
Il m'arrive de réaliser des documents bancaires pour Raj.
The Koothrappalis aren'tjust rich, they're Richie Rich rich.
Les Koothrappalis sont richissimes,$ riches de chez riches.
Well, so how much is that?
C‘est a dire ?
About halfway between Bruce Wayne and Scrooge McDuck.
Quelque part entre Bruce Wayne et l'Oncle Picsou.
The last time we went to the zoo...
Quand on est allés au zoo,
...that son of a bitch made me buy him a churro.
ce fumier m‘a forcé à lui payer un churro.
I'm sorry. I don't mean to be rude, but I need to go call Raj's sister...
Pardon. Je dois appeler la sœur de Raj,
...who I love so much.
que j'aime tendrement.
Okay, so he's got money, and it's a few gifts, and a car.
Ok, il est riche et il lui fait quelques cadeaux. Dont une voiture.
And she got him to pay off all her credit cards.
Elle lui a fait rembourser tous ses crédits.
What? He paid off her credit cards?
Quoi ? Ses crédits consos ?
Damn it, I could have dated Raj for a couple months.
Merde, j'aurais pu sortir avec Raj.
But I wouldn't have because I'm not that kind of girl. We should really talk to Raj.
Mais je ne l'ai pas fait, c‘est pas mon genre. Il faut qu'on parle a Raj.
He's not gonna listen, he's in love.
Il n'écoutera pas. Il est amoureux.
Can't figure out what to do? I remember those days.
Vous êtes perdus ? Je le fus aussi, jadis.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have to...
Excusez-moi, je dois...
...stay right here.
Rester ici.
I'm the one that introduced him to her. I've gotta say something.
Non, c‘est moi qui les ai présentés. Je dois intervenir.
-You're engaged to my friend. -Hey, Bernadette doesn't mind...
- Tu es fiancé à mon amie. - Bernadette se fiche
...where I get my motor running, as long as I park in the right garage.
de ce qui lance mon moteur, du moment que je me gare chez elle.
I can't believe you're engaged to my friend.
J'en reviens pas que tu sois fiancé à mon amie.
[WHISPERS] Oh, here she comes.
Elle arrive.
Smart. Whisper, so the deaf chick can't hear you.
Malin : tu chuchotes pour éviter que la sourde t'entende.
-[IN NORMAL VOICE] Hi. -Oh, hey. Hi. Nice to see you.
- Salut. - Salut, je suis contente de te voir.
Um, can we talk to you about Raj?
On peut parler de Raj ?
She says, "Sure, what about him?"
“Oui, qu‘y a-t-il ?"
Okay. Um, gosh, how do I start?
Ok, par où je commence ?
He hasn't dated a whole lot of women.
Il n‘a pas eu beaucoup de copines.
And I'm concerned that, without meaning to...
J'ai peur que sans le vouloir,
...you might be taking advantage of him.
tu profites un peu de lui.
By letting him buy you a bunch of expensive things.
En le laissant te faire des cadeaux luxueux.
l-- Howard, focus.
Howard, on se concentre.
-Tell her what I'm saying. -Right.
- Traduis. - D‘accord.
Are you a gold digger or not?
T'es la pour le blé ?
Oh, something, something. Who the something do you think you are?
"Truc, truc. Tu te prends pour qui, sale truc."
Mind your own something business and go something yourself.
"Occupe-toi de ton truc et va te faire truc."
Oh, ha, ha, wait, I got this now.
Attends, j'ai compris.
-l'm so mad at you. -Okay, wait.
- Je suis furieux. - Attends.
How dare you ambush my girlfriend at the gym?
Tu as piégé ma copine àla salle de sport.
We didn't mean for it to be an ambush.
On ne voulait pas la piéger.
It's kind of impossible not to sneak up on deaf people.
Mais c‘est dur de ne pas surprendre une sourde.
And, hey, since when are you so chatty?
Et depuis quand tu parles tant ?
-l'm hammered. -Raj, come here.
- Je suis bourré. - Raj, viens.
This girl is trouble.
Cette fille n‘est pas nette.
What kind of relationship is it where you buy her gifts and she gives you sex?
C‘est quoi ce rapport ? Tu offres des cadeaux, elle offre du sexe ?
The best one I've ever had.
Le meilleur que j‘aie jamais eu.
Okay, come on, you know you can do better.
Arrête, tu sais que tu mérites mieux.
I see what's going on here.
J'ai compris.
You and I had our crazy night together.
Après notre nuit de folie,
And now you can't stand to see me with another woman.
tu ne supportes pas de me voir avec une autre.
It's okay, I can't get mad at your feelings.
Je ne peux pas te reprocher tes sentiments.
I don't have feelings.
Je n'en ai pas.
Yeah, that's good. Keep telling yourself that.
Elle est bonne. Essaie un peu de t'en convaincre.
He is cuter now that I know he's rich.
Il est plus beau maintenant qu'il est riche.
l have a surprise for you. Cover your eyes.
J'ai une surprise. Ferme les yeux.
Open them.
Ouvre.
It's a real ruby.
C‘est un vrai rubis.
It was a little expensive, but no one can put a price on love.
Un peu cher, mais l‘amour n‘a pas de prix.
Although the people at Cartier took a pretty good shot at it.
Ça n‘empêche pas Cartier de le facturer.
Oh, Mummy, Daddy, what a nice surprise.
Maman, papa, quelle bonne surprise.
No, it's not a nice surprise, it's a bad surprise.
Non, c‘est une très mauvaise surprise.
-Penny called us. -Pe n ny?
Penny nous a appelés.
She told us you're spending all our money on your new girlfriend.
Elle dit que tu dépenses notre argent pour la copine.
I just got her a couple of things.
J'ai juste fait un ou deux cadeaux.
She gives me things too.
Elie m'en fait aussi.
Yeah, yeah. I'm a gynecologist. I know exactly what she gives you.
Je suis gynéco, je sais ce qu‘elle le donne.
You need to ï¬nd a nice Indian girl from a good family.
Trouve une gentille indienne de bonne famille.
If you keep seeing this woman, you're cut 017'.
Quitte-la ou on le coupe les vivres.
What? You're gonna make me choose between the woman I love...
Que je choisisse entre la femme que j'aime
...and the money I have very strong feelings for?
et l'argent que j'aime aussi ?
It's up to you.
À toi de voir.
-Well, I choose love. -Heh, you're an idiot.
- Je choisis l'amour. - Tu es un idiot.
Love doesn't last.
L‘amour ne dure pas.
Well, he's going to ï¬nd out eventually.
Ille découvrira tôt ou tard.
Think about it.
Réﬂéchis,
My, uh, parents are making me choose between money and you.
Mes parents me demandent de choisir entre toi et l‘argent.
I choose you.
Je t'ai choisie.
No. I think we'll have to return the car.
Non, on va devoir rendre la voiture.
And the necklace. Yeah, that too.
Et le collier. Oui, ça aussi.
But none of those things matter because we have something better.
Mais peu importe. On garde le plus précieux.
We have love.
Notre amour.
-Oh, Penny, I hurt so bad. -Uh--
Penny, j'ai si mal.
I know. I know.
Je sais, je sais.
Sometimes I put the TV on mute just to pretend she's still with me.
Parfois je mets la télé en sourdine pour faire comme si elle était la.
But I can't watch the closed-captioning without crying.
Mais les sous-titres pour malentendants me font pleurer.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Je suis navrée.
lwish I could make you feel better.
J'aimerais te remonter le moral.
Seriously?
Sérieusement ?
I'm heartbroken and you're hitting on me?
J'ai le cœur brisé, et tu me dragues ?
What? No.
Quoi ? Non.
Look, Penny, you're great, but I had a long talk with my parents.
Penny, tu es super, mais j'ai parlé avec mes parents.
And they said ifl date an Indian girl, I get a Maserati.
Si je sors avec une indienne, j‘aurai une Maserati.
...even though I can't have sex with you.
bien queje ne puisse pas coucher avec toi.
Try throwing it in the microwave for a few seconds.
Essaie de le mettre vite fait au micro-ondes.
Should I use the restroom or wait until we get home?
Je vais aux toilettes ou j‘attends ?
Come on, Papa needs to void his bladder.
Allez, j'ai une vessie à vider.
Oh, that's not what you wanna see after three buttermilks.
J'espérais autre chose, après trois petits laits.
Here you go, boys. I'll pick it up when you're ready.
Et voilà. Je repasserai.
-Thanks for dinner, buddy. -Yeah, real big of you.
- Merci pour le dîner. - C‘est sympa.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Vite, Vite, Vite.
Oh, don't cheap out on the tip. We all know you're loaded now.
Sois pas radin sur le pourboire. On sait que t'es blindé.
[English - us - an]
[French]